Register to The Karl Weigl Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Music by Karl Weigl, I.A
    - Vocal Music
      - Cantatas
        - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Chorus score. English]
          - The four seasons: little cantata for children's or women's chorus with piano / compiled and arranged from old folktunes, songs, and dances by Karl and Vally Weigl; English translations by V. Weigl., 1 manuscript chorus score (16 p.); 26 cm. (Box 2, Folder 35)
            Photocopy of an undated manuscript chorus score.
          - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Chorus score. English] (Box 2, Folder 36)
          - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Chorus score. English] (Box 2, Folder 37)
            Title changed in manuscript to "The four seasons: little cantata for children's voices and piano, on old folktunes of various lands".
        - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Es ist ein Ros entsprungen]
          - [Es ist ein Ros entsprungen], 1 fragment of manuscript music (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 2, Folder 38)
            Photocopy of an undated manuscript fragment.
            English translation and other annotations in manuscript.
        - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Es ist ein Ros entsprungen. English]
          - Lo, how a rose e'er blooming / arrangement by Vally Weigl., 1 manuscript score (1 sheet); 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 39)
          - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Es ist ein Ros entsprungen. English] (Box 2, Folder 40)
        - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Libretto]
          - [Notes on sources for music and text in Die vier Jahreszeiten]., 1 leaf; 29 cm. (Box 2, Folder 41)
            In manuscript.
            In German.
        - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Libretto. English]
          - The four seasons: little cantata for children's or women's chorus with piano accompaniment / compiled and arranged from old folktunes, songs and dances, by Karl and Vally Weigl; English words by Vally Weigl., 7 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 42)
          - [Vier Jahreszeiten. Libretto. English] (Box 2, Folder 43)
            Carbon copy of above.
        - [Weltfeier]
          - Weltfeier: symphonische Kantate für Tenor und hohen Bass (soli), gemischten Chor und Orchester / Karl Weigl; Text nach Gedichten von Heinrich Hart., 1 manuscript score (251 p.); 35 cm. (Box 2, Folder 44)
            Holograph, signed, undated.
            "Leihmaterial ... B. Schott's Söhne, Mainz" - stamp.
            Annotations in holograph.
          - [Weltfeier] (Box 2, Folder 45)
            Photocopy of above.
            "Belwin-Mills Publ. Corp. ... Rental Library" - stamp.
          - [Weltfeier. Vocal score] Reproduced by Independent Music Publishers, New York City. (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
            One score in 2 v.
          - Weltfeier: symphonische Kantate nach Gedichten von Heinrich Hart: für Tenor- und Bariton-Solo, gemischten Chor und grosses Orchestra: Opus 17 / komponiert von Karl Weigl. Mainz: B. Schott's Söhne, c1924., 1 vocal score (91 p.); 27 cm. (Box 3, Folder 48)
            Plate no.: 31113.
          - [Weltfeier] (Box 3, Folder 49)
            Music quotation, holograph, signed and dated 1925, on cover.
          - [Weltfeier] (Box 3, Folder 50)
            "World Festival" -- in manuscript.
            "American Composers Alliance Library" - stamp.
          - [Weltfeier] (Box 3, Folder 52)
            "Nänie" and "Gesprach mit dem Tode" include English translation in manuscript.
            English translation in manuscript.
        - [Weltfeier. Vocal score. English & German]
          - Weltfeier = World festival / Karl Weigl; words adapted from poems of Heinrich Hart; translated into English by Luise Haessler., 1 manuscript vocal score (45 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 53)
            Solo and choral parts, with German words and English translation, undated.
          - [Weltfeier. Vocal score. English & German] (Box 3, Folder 54)
          - [Weltfeier. Vocal score. English & German] (Box 3, Folder 55)
            "Nänie" and "Gesprach mit dem Tode" only.
        - [Weltfeier. Gesprach mit dem Tode. Vocal score]
          - [Weltfeier. Libretto. German] [Fragment from Gesprach mit dem Tode]., 1 fragment of a manuscript vocal score ([8] p.); 35 cm. (Box 3, Folder 56)
            Undated manuscript fragment.
          - Weltfeier / nach Gedichten von Heinrich Hart; zusammengestellt von Karl Weigl., 5 p.; 29 cm. (Box 3, Folder 57)
          - Weltfeier = "Worlds festival" / German poetries by Henrich Hart; compiled and completed by Karl Weigl; music by Karl Weigl., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 58)
            Typescript.
        - [Weltfeier. Libretto. English]
          - World festival / music by Karl Weigl; words adapted from poems of Heinrich Hart; translated into English by Luise Haessler., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 59)
            Typescript, with manuscript annotations, undated.
          - World festival / music by Karl Weigl; words adapted from poems of Heinrich Hart; translated into English by Luise Haessler., 4 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 60)
            Typescript, carbon, with manuscript annotations, undated.
          - [Fragments of an English translation of Weltfeier]. (Box 3, Folder 61)
            2 items.
      - Choral Music
        - [Black cat]
          - Black cat: for 4-part mixed chorus / Karl Weigl; [text by] Nancy Byrd Turner., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 40 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1026)
            "Karl Weigl" changed to "Pygmalion" in manuscript.
          - [Black cat] (Box 31, Folder 1027)
            Same photocopy as above
            "c1946."
            "Partly corrected copy."
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 27. Heimweh]
          - Heimweh: für vierstimmigen Männerchor a cappella / von Karl Weigl; [text by] Ricarda Huch., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 34 cm. (Box 4, Folder 62)
            Undated manuscript score.
          - 3 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Heimweh, op. 27, No. 1 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Ricarda Huch. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (5 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 63)
            Plate number U.E. 10.411.
          - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 27. Heimweh] (Box 4, Folder 64)
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 27. Säerspruch]
          - 3 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Säerspruch: op. 27, No. 2 / Karl Weigl; [text by] C. F. Mayer. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (4 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 65)
            Plate number U.E. 10.412.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 27. Waldesstimme]
          - 3 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Waldesstimme: op. 27, No. 3 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Peter Hille. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (6 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 66)
            Plate number U.E. 10.413.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 27. Texts. English.]
          See [Choral music. Selections. Texts. English]
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Lob der Faulheit]
          - 4 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Lob der Faulheit: op. 28, No. 1 / Karl Weigl; [text by] G. E. Lessing. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (4 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 67)
            Plate number U.E. 10.414.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Firnelicht]
          - 4 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). No. 2 Firnelicht: op. 28, No. 2 / Karl Weigl; [text by] C. F. Mayer. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (5 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 68)
            Plate number U.E. 10.415.
          - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Firnelicht] (Box 4, Folder 69)
            Photocopy of above with English translation by Vally Weigl.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Abendtrunk]
          - 4 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Abendtrunk: op. 28, No. 3 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Will Vesper. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (2 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 70)
            Plate number U.E. 10.416.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Nachtmusikanten]
          - 4 Männerchöre a cappella (4 stg). Nachtmusikanten: op. 28, No. 4 / Karl Weigl; [text from] Wunderhorn. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (9 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 71)
            Plate number U.E. 10.417.
          - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Nachtmusikanten] (Box 4, Folder 72)
            English translation in manuscript and on accompanying typescript sheet.
        - [Choruses, men's voices, op. 28. Texts. English.]
        - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 25. Selections]
          - Vier 3-stimmige Frauenchöre a capella / Weigl., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 73)
            Includes numbers 1, 3, 4, and 8.
          - 8 Frauenchöre a capella (3 u. 4 stg.), op. 25, Heft 1 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (9 p.); 29 cm. (Box 4, Folder 74)
            Includes numbers 1-4.
            Plate number U.E. 10.408.
            English translation by Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - 8 Frauenchöre a capella (3 u. 4 stg.), op. 25, Heft 2 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (8 p.); 29 cm. (Box 4, Folder 75)
            Includes numbers 5-8.
            Plate number U.E. 10.409.
            Number 5 includes second stanza with English translation in manuscript.
          - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 25. Selections] (Box 4, Folder 76)
          - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 25. Selections] (Box 4, Folder 77)
            Photocopy of above with English translation by Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 25. Selections] (Box 4, Folder 78)
        - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 25. Texts. English]
          See also [Choral music. Selections. Texts. English]
          - [Texts] (Box 4, Folder 79)
            6 items.
            English translations by Vally Weigl.
            Typescript, carbon and photocopy, and manuscript, n.d.
        - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 26]
          - Vöglein Schwermut; Liebesreime / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (7 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 80)
          - 2 Frauenchöre a cappella (4 stg.), op. 26 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, n.d., 1 score (9 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 81)
            Plate no.: U. E. 10.410.
        - [Choruses, women's voices, op. 26. Texts. English]
          - [Texts] (Box 4, Folder 82)
            4 items.
            Typescript, carbon, and manuscript, n.d
        - [Early Easter morning]
          See also Songs
          - Shouting sun / Karl Weigl; poem by Nancy Byrd Turner., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 39 cm. (Box 4, Folder 83)
            Author of text written as "Nancy Bird Turner."
            Photocopy of an undated manuscript score of the version of Early Easter Morning for solo voice and piano.
            Parts for chorus, SATB, added in manuscript.
          - Shouting sun / Karl Weigl; poem by Nancy Byrd Turner., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 38 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1028)
            For chorus, SATB.
            "Two Choral Songs on Southern Poems" -- in caption in manuscript.
          - [Early Easter morning] (Box 31, Folder 1029)
            "c1945."
          - [Early Easter morning] (Box 31, Folder 1030)
            "American Composers Alliance Library."
          - Early Easter morning = Früh am Ostermorgen: for S.A.T.B., or solo, and piano / Karl Weigl; [text by] Nancy Byrd Turner; German version by Vally Weigl. Melville, N.Y.: Belwin Mills, c1974., 1 score (11 p.); 26 cm. (Box 4, Folder 84)
            Plate no.: OCT 2306.
        - [Fanfarenlied]
          See [Lied zu Gott dem Herrn]
        - [Frühlingsfeier]
          - Frühlingsfeier: für 4 stimmigen Frauenchor u. Orchester / [text] v. Heinrich Heine / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (19 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 85)
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 6]
          - Drei Gedichte von Lenau für achtstimmigen gemischten Chor a cappella, op. 6 / von Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1912., 1 score (19 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 86)
            Publisher's no.: 3587.
            Plate no.: U. E. 3587.
          - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 6] (Box 4, Folder 87)
            Photocopy of above, without cover, with English translation by Luise Haessler.
          - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 6] (Box 4, Folder 88)
            Photocopy of above, without cover or title page.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 6. Texts. English & German]
          - [Texts] (Box 4, Folder 89)
            English translations by Luise Haessler.
            Manuscript and typescript, 1941, n.d.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7]
          - Vier Gedichte für gemischten Chor (a capella), op. 7 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1912., 1 score (9 p.); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 90)
            Plate no.: U. E. 3588.
            Photocopy without title page.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7. Komm, süsser Tod]
          - Come, gentle death: for (divided) four-part chorus of mixed voices a capella: op. 7, no. 1 / Karl Weigl; English words by Luise Haessler. New York: Associated Music Publishers; Vienna: Universal Edition, c1912, 1942., 1 score (4 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 91)
            Includes keyboard accompaniment for rehearsal only.
            English words.
            Caption title.
            Plate no.: U.E. 3588a.
            Includes separate text.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7. Campo Santo di Staglieno]
          - In the cemetery at Staglieno = Campo Santo di Staglieno: for four-part chorus of mixed voices a capella: op. 7, no. 2 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Friedrich Nietzsche; English version by Luise Haessler. New York: Associated Music Publishers; Vienna: Universal Edition, c1912, 1942., 1 score (4 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 92)
            English and German words.
            Plate no.: U.E. 3588b.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7. Glaube]
          - Faith = Glaube: for four-part chorus of mixed voices a capella: op. 7, no. 3 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Friedrich Lienhard; English version by Luise Haessler. New York: Associated Music Publishers; Vienna: Universal Edition, c1912, 1942., 1 score (4 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
            Plate no.: U.E. 3588c.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7. Morgen]
          - A song of freedom = Morgen: for (divided) four-part chorus of mixed voices a capella: op. 7, no. 4 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Gottfried Keller; English version by Vally Weigl. New York: Associated Music Publishers; Vienna: Universal Edition, c1912, 1942., 1 score (5 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 94)
            Plate no.: U.E. 3588d.
        - [Gedichte, mixed voices, op. 7. Texts. English & German]
          See also Hull, Mrs. in Correspondence
          - [Texts] (Box 4, Folder 95)
            Includes English translations by Vally Weigl and Elizabeth Norman Hapgood.
            Typescript, carbon, and manuscript, n.d.
        - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Ode]
          - Zwei geistliche Gesänge = Two religious songs. No. 1. Ode: op. 14 / [text by] Claudius; Karl Weigl. Mainz: B. Schott's Söhne, c1924., 1 score (32 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 96)
            For four part double choir a capella.
            English words by Ada Rosenthal.
            Plate no.: 31103a.
          - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Ode] (Box 4, Folder 97)
            Includes title page for both songs.
          - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Ode] (Box 4, Folder 98)
        - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Hymne]
          - Zwei geistliche Gesänge. No. 2. Hymne = Two religious songs. Hymn: op. 14 / [text from] Wunderhorn; Karl Weigl. Mainz: B. Schott's Söhne, c1924., 1 score (36 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 99)
            Plate no.: 31103b.
          - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Hymne] (Box 4, Folder 100)
          - [Geistliche Gesänge, op. 14. Hymne] (Box 4, Folder 101)
        - [In the MacDowell Woods, op. 34]
          - In the MacDowell Woods: for 6 part mixed chorus / by Karl Weigl; words by Nancy Byrd Turner., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 102)
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed, Bass River, 1942 Aug 15, "dedicated to Mrs. Edward MacDowell."
            "Reference copy."
          - In the Mac Dowell Woods: for six-part chorus of mixed voices a cappella: op. 34 / music by Karl Weigl; words by Nancy Byrd Turner. Boston: Boston Music, c1942., 1 score (7 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 103)
            Choral art series.
            Title from caption; cover lists other works.
            Plate no.: B.M.Co.10207.
            Publisher no.: 2372.
        - [Kinderlieder]
          - 6 children's songs: for 2 part children's or women's chorus (or solo) and piano: op. 11 / Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith and Vally Weigl., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 104)
        - [Klarer Liebesstern]
          - Klarer Liebesstern., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 33 cm. (Box 4, Folder 105)
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed, 1912 Jul 12.
        - [Lied zu Gott dem Herrn]
          - Das Lied zu Gott dem Herrn. Das Fanfarenlied / Hans Reinthaler; verl. v. Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 27 x 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 106)
            For four part chorus.
        - [Natur, op. 29]
          - Natur = Nature: für 8 stimm. gem. Chor a cappella: op. 29 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Heinrich Hart. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 1 score (20 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 107)
            Words in German and English.
            Caption title; cover lists other works.
            Plate no.: U. E. 10.534.
            Publisher's no.: U. E. Nr. 10.534.
        - [Psalm 48]
          - Hymn: based on Psalm 48., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 38 cm. (Box 4, Folder 108)
            For four-part chorus.
          - [Psalm 48] (Box 4, Folder 109)
            "Karl Weigl" -- in manuscript in caption.
          - Psalm 48., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 110)
            "Pacemaker" -- in caption.
          - [Psalm 48] (Box 4, Folder 111)
            "Vernon La ..." -- in manuscript in caption.
        - [Psalm 84, no. 1]
          - Psalm 84., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 15 x 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 112)
            "Columbus I" -- in caption.
        - [Psalm 84, no. 2]
          - Psalm 84., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 23 x 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 113)
            "Columbus II" -- in caption.
        - [Psalm 150, no. 1]
          - [Psalm 150], 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 114)
            Psalm 150; Psalm 150.
            "Columbus I" and "Columbus II" -- in captions.
        - [Psalm 150, no. 2]
          See [Psalm 150, no. 1]
        - [Religious choruses. Who knows?]
          - Who knows? = Wer weiss? / Karl Weigl; author [of text] unknown, Geneva around 1551; English translation by Florence M. [i.e. L.?] Kite., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 115)
            "Op. 35."
            "Dedicated to Dr. Wilbur K. Thomas and our Philadelphia friends."
          - Who knows? / Karl Weigl; author [of text] unknown, Geneva around 1551; English poem by Florence L. Kite. New York: Associated Music Publishers, c1953., 1 score (10 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 116)
            Includes piano part for rehearsal only.
            Words in English and German.
            Title from caption; cover includes both choruses.
            "To Wilbur K. Thomas and the Carl Schurz Foundation."
            Publisher's no.: A-175.
          - [Religious choruses. Who knows?] (Box 4, Folder 117)
        - [Religious choruses. Hymn]
          - Hymn for 4 part chorus a capella / Karl Weigl; words by John Masefield., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 118)
          - [Religious choruses. Hymn] (Box 4, Folder 119)
            "Karl Weigl" changed to "Berkeley" in manuscript.
          - [Religious choruses. Hymn] (Box 4, Folder 120)
            "Piano or organ for rehearsals."
            German translation by Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - [Religious choruses. Hymn] (Box 4, Folder 121)
            Same photocopy as above with part for piano or organ and German translation by Vally Weigl.
          - Hymn / Karl Weigl; word by John Masefield; German translation by Vally Weigl. New York: Associated Music Publishers, c1953., 1 score (7 p.); 27 cm. (Box 4, Folder 122)
            Publisher's no.: A-176.
        - [Religious choruses of our time]
          - Two choruses of the time / Karl Weigl; poems by J. G. Whittier., 1 manuscript score (10 p.); 36 cm. (Box 5, Folder 123)
            Contents: "Hymn of the Time" and "Thy Will Be Done."
            Photocopy of holograph scores, signed, Bass River, 1942 Aug 19-29.
            Title from cover in manuscript.
          - [Religious choruses of our time] (Box 5, Folder 124)
            Same photocopy of "Thy Will Be Done" as above.
            "Sentinel" in caption in manuscript.
          - [Religious choruses of our time] (Box 5, Folder 125)
            "Two Songs of the Time" -- in manuscript on cover.
          - [Religious choruses of our time] (Box 5, Folder 126)
            Same photocopy of "Hymn" as above.
            "Two Religious Choruses of the Time" -- in manuscript in caption.
        - [Riese]
          - Der Riese: für vierstimmig. gem. Chor u. Klavier / [text by] Henckell; K. W., 1 manuscript score (13 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 127)
            Includes separate text of poem.
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed, 1927 May 10.
        - [So spricht der Wald]
          - So spricht der Wald: für 4 stimmigen Männerchor a cappella / text von Karl Schneller., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 34 cm. (Box 5, Folder 128)
            Undated holograph score.
            "Keinwort: 'Wienerwald'."
          - So spricht der Wald: für 4 stimmigen Männerchor a cappella / text von Karl Schneller., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 129)
        - [Watchman's report]
          - The watchman's report / Karl Weigl; [text by] John Bowring., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 28 cm. (Box 5, Folder 130)
            For baritone, chorus, SATB, and piano.
            "Based on the chorale 'Sleepers Awake'."
            "Dedicated to Germantown Friends School."
            Photocopy of a holograph score, no year, Jan 19.
          - The watchman's report = Wächter's Botschaft: op. 39 / Karl Weigl; [text by] John Bowring; German translation, Vally Weigl. New York: John Markert, c1955., 1 score (12 p.); 24 cm. (Box 5, Folder 131)
            For baritone solo, chorus, SATB, and piano.
            "To the Germantown Friends School."
          - [Watchman's report] (Box 5, Folder 132)
            "American Composers Edition."
        - [Choral music. Selections. Texts. English]
          See also [Songs. Selections. Texts] in Songs
          - [Texts] (Box 5, Folder 133)
            12 items.
            English translations of texts from choruses, op. 25, op. 27, and op. 28.
            Typescript, n.d.
      - Songs
        - [Alt deutsches Weihnachtslied]
          - Alt deutsches Weihnachtslied = Old German Christmas song / bearbeitet von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 134)
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed and dated 1943 Oct 15.
        - [And there you stood]
          - And there you stood ... / Karl Weigl; [text by] Michael Orogo. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 5, Folder 135)
            "For Baritone" -- in manuscript.
        - [Black cat]
          See also Choral Music
          - Black cat / Karl Weigl; [text by] Nancy Byrd Turner., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 41 cm. (Box 31, Folder 1031)
          - [Black cat] (Box 5, Folder 136)
            "Music belonging to Howard Crank" -- original folder.
        - [Children's songs]
          - Children's songs / by Karl Weigl; words by Vally Weigl., 1 ms score (9 p.); 35 cm. (Box 5, Folder 137)
            Photocopy of a holograph score; first song signed and dated 1944 Jul 11.
            "6 children's songs, for Peggy" -- in manuscript.
          - [Children's songs] (Box 5, Folder 138)